Tiana Hayden

<u>tiana.hayden@me.com</u> | (760) 715-5839 3550 Lebon Drive, Unit 6317, San Diego, CA 92122

SUMMARY

I bring a customer-first mindset to whatever I do, whether that's direct account customer support, customer-guided product feedback, or internal training creation and delivery. I have experience in online account management, internal and external product support, product and operations improvement, and product training creation and delivery.

EXPERIENCE

Google - Subject Matter Expert, AdWords Troubleshooting

Dublin, Ireland

December 2015 - Present

- Resolve second-level support escalations from Google's frontline AdWords support agents. Answer advanced product specific questions and solve the toughest issues for Google's online advertisers.
- Enhance support agent's team knowledge and improve customer experience through training creation/ delivery, resource management, and product improvement.
- Bring the voice of the customer to Product and Eng teams to improve the product and push for feature updates.
- Work cross functionally with the Product and Operations teams to transition product launches and workflow changes.

Google - Account Strategist, AdWords

Mountain View, California

August 2014 - December 2015

- Delivered outstanding customer experience to Google's advertisers, publishers, and/or users. Demonstrated product knowledge in Google AdWords, Google Analytics, YouTube, Google Merchant Center, and Google Partners. Provided strategic and consultative advice for client's online presence.
- Collaborated with the AdWords Help Center team to update content and promote the Help Center's Educational Platform.
- Implemented creative ways to improve customer relationships and increase growth by promoting Google products.

Advanced Brain Monitoring - Engagement and Communications Coordinator

Carlsbad, CA

September 2013 - August 2014

- Sold advanced Neurotechnology equipment to medical institutions and academic researchers. Managed existing and new customer relationships, developed new customer acquisition strategies, and supported users throughout the buying cycle.
- Developed new user training material for education on hardware and software.
 Created and sourced written content, product images, and video.

Apple - Specialist

La Jolla, CA

April 2012 - December 2013

- Delivered outstanding customer experience for Apple's customer through in-store sales and technical support. Presented Apple's best solutions in products and services to consumers and businesses.
- Led in-store workshops on iPhone, iPad and iCloud. Taught users how to use Apple's products and services and presented the appropriate resource for further education.

EDUCATION

University of San Diego - Bachelor of Arts, Psychology

August 2009 - May 2013

Graduated Magna Cum Laude, 3.74 Overall GPA. Minored in Business Administration Studied abroad at CEA Global Campus, Barcelona Spain, Fall 2011

AWARDS

Won Google's Q4 '15 Gold Award for impact on Global Customer Experience team Completed Google's 2 year <u>Business Associate (BA) Program</u>

Won University of San Diego's Department of Psychological Sciences Honors Convocation Award for Outstanding Student Research

Won the Western Psychological Association Student Scholarship Award for Best Student Paper